<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ADIL SADQI</title>
	<atom:link href="https://web.adil.asadqi.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com</link>
	<description>Welcome to My Personal Webpage. you are in the right place to get in touch with me !</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Elon Musk just brought an infamous neo-Nazi back to Twitter</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-just-brought-an-infamous-neo-nazi-back-to-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-just-brought-an-infamous-neo-nazi-back-to-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-just-brought-an-infamous-neo-nazi-back-to-twitter/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ye might have crossed the line by tweeting a swastika superimposed with a Star of David, but you can’t blame other Nazi apologists for getting mixed signals. On Thursday night, Musk personally intervened after the artist formerly known as Kanye West shared the symbol. “I tried my best,” Musk tweeted in response to a tweet [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ye might have <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/elon-musk-suspends-kanye-wests-account-for-breaking-twitter-rules/">crossed the line</a> by tweeting a swastika superimposed with a Star of David, but you can’t blame other Nazi apologists for getting mixed signals.</p>
<p>On Thursday night, Musk personally intervened after the artist <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/10/09/kanye-west-twitter-elon-musk/">formerly known as Kanye West</a> shared the symbol. “I tried my best,” Musk tweeted in response to a tweet raising alarm at <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/10/09/kanye-west-twitter-elon-musk/">West’s behavior</a>. “Despite that, he again violated our rule against incitement to violence. Account will be suspended.”</p>
<p>On Truth Social, West shared a screenshot that indicates he was only suspended from Twitter for 12 hours — a relatively lenient sentence. But West’s account was still suspended as of 1 PM PT on Friday.</p>
<p>Hours prior to his suspension, West openly elaborated his antisemitic beliefs in an interview with Alex Jones. West appeared wearing a full mask on the show and praised Hitler, repeatedly declared his “love” of Nazis and doubled down when a visibly uncomfortable Jones gave him a chance to backtrack.</p>
<p>As Nazi-related hashtags take over Twitter’s trending topics, the <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/24/easy-come-easy-go-daily-stormer-briefly-reappears-on-dreamhost-before-being-banned-again/">infamous neo-Nazi Andrew Anglin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/RightWingWatch/status/1598719032764555264">also re-appeared on the site</a>, tweeting from a new handle associated with the account he had banned back in 2015. Anglin, who created the white supremacist website The Daily Stormer, probed Twitter’s new rules in a reply to Musk. “Ye caught a 12 hour suspension for tweeting a Star of David with a swastika in it… Whatever the rules are, people will follow them. We just need to know what the rules are.”</p>
<p>Anglin was <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/15/after-charlottesville-more-web-service-providers-ditch-the-daily-stormer-for-tos-violations/">de-platformed from the broader internet</a> when companies providing The Daily Stormer’s web hosting, DDoS protection and other utilities cut off their services back in 2017. That push against the site, which is named after a Nazi propaganda paper, came after the Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville raised alarm about a rising tide of open white supremacy in the U.S. In a speech he wrote that was read aloud at the rally (Anglin wasn’t present), Anglin warned that he and his supporters would soon be “digging graves” and called for death to “enemies of the white race.”</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/15/after-charlottesville-more-web-service-providers-ditch-the-daily-stormer-for-tos-violations/">After Charlottesville, more web service providers ditch The Daily Stormer for TOS violations</a></p>
<div class="piano-inline-promo"></div>

</div>
<p>Anglin’s fans quickly welcomed him back to the platform. One account with an obvious reference to white supremacy in its handle tweeted that it was checking in for duty. Other neo-Nazi and white supremacist accounts criticized Musk’s action against West, characterizing them as an unexpected betrayal.</p>
<p>Richard Spencer is also benefiting from Musk’s changes at Twitter. Spencer, a <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/11/23/1058024314/charlottesville-unite-the-right-trial-verdict" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Unite the Right organizer</a> and an open white nationalist who has greeted supporters with the Nazi salute, is now a verified Twitter user who pays for a Twitter Blue monthly subscription. Spencer is currently promoting a Twitter Space declaring “Ye-ism triumphant.”</p>
<p>Twitter’s pre-Musk policy against hateful conduct is still online, but the company’s new owner mostly appears to be winging it lately. Last week, Musk conducted a Twitter poll of his followers and <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/24/musk-says-twitter-will-offer-amnesty-to-suspended-accounts/">later declared “amnesty”</a> for any accounts that “have not broken the law or engaged in egregious spam.” That decision set up potentially thousands of accounts that previously violated Twitter’s policies against hate and harassment to be restored to the platform.</p>
<p>Musk’s one-man approach to content moderation is unlikely to scale. The billionaire Tesla and SpaceX CEO slashed Twitter’s moderation teams when he took over at the company last month. He also lost Twitter’s Global Head of Trust &amp; Safety Yoel Roth who helped steer the company through many of its thorniest policy decisions in recent years. “One of my limits was if Twitter starts being ruled by dictatorial edict rather than by policy… there’s no longer a need for me in my role, doing what I do,” Roth said in his first <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4l1INc-rM5M" target="_blank" rel="noopener">post-departure interview this week</a>.</p>
<p>In spite of his early promises for a<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/10/28/elon-musk-twitter-trump-content-moderation-council/"> policy-making council</a>, so far Musk is relying on unscientific Twitter polls skewed toward his supporters to set the platform’s rules. According to <a href="https://www.adl.org/resources/blog/extremists-far-right-figures-exploit-recent-changes-twitter" target="_blank" rel="noopener">research</a> from the ADL, white supremacists and other extremists noticed the opportunity and encouraged their supporters to vote in Musk’s “amnesty” poll on Telegram.</p>
<p>One Telegram channel with thousands of followers cautioned members who planned to head back to Twitter: “Refrain from obvious slurs; don’t make it easy for them.”</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/10/09/kanye-west-twitter-elon-musk/">Twitter locks Kanye West’s account for antisemitic tweet following warm Elon Musk welcome</a></p>

</div>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/24/musk-says-twitter-will-offer-amnesty-to-suspended-accounts/">Musk says Twitter will offer ‘amnesty’ to suspended accounts</a></p>

</div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/elon-musk-nazis-kanye-twitter-andrew-anglin/">Elon Musk just brought an infamous neo-Nazi back to Twitter</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/taylor-hatmaker/">Taylor Hatmaker</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-just-brought-an-infamous-neo-nazi-back-to-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Daily Crunch: ChatGPT’s user experience and implementation ‘should have Google scared’</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/daily-crunch-chatgpts-user-experience-and-implementation-should-have-google-scared/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/daily-crunch-chatgpts-user-experience-and-implementation-should-have-google-scared/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/daily-crunch-chatgpts-user-experience-and-implementation-should-have-google-scared/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important stories delivered to your inbox every day at 3 p.m. PDT, subscribe here. Heeeey! Today has been a fun, rich, and varied day of news on your favorite tech news site. Haje got the unfortunate news that he will be attending his 15th CES in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important stories delivered to your inbox every day at 3 p.m. PDT,</em><a href="http://link.techcrunch.com/join/134/signup-all-newsletters"> <em>subscribe here</em></a><em>.</em></p>
<p>Heeeey! Today has been a fun, rich, and varied day of news on your favorite tech news site. Haje got the unfortunate news that he will be attending his 15th CES in Las Vegas, so if you’re going with your startup, <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/">the TC hardware team wants to hear from you</a>. Oh, and we have a slew of gift guides coming up — <a href="https://techcrunch.com/tag/gift-guide-2022">here’s a sneaky preview for the first few</a>, if you want some inspiration for getting the jump on your holiday shopping. — <a href="https://twitter.com/ChristineMHall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Christine</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/haje" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Haje</a></p>
<h2>The TechCrunch Top 3</h2>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/openais-chatgpt-shows-why-implementation-is-key-with-generative-ai/"><strong>The answers to all of life’s important questions</strong></a>: Generative artificial intelligence has come a long way, and many of our colleagues took OpenAI’s ChatGPT for a ride, including <a href="https://twitter.com/etherington" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Darrell</a>, who asked the all-important question about Pokémon strengths and weaknesses. While you’re at it, check out <a href="https://twitter.com/kyle_l_wiggers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kyle</a>’s story on OpenAI’s <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/while-anticipation-builds-for-gpt-4-openai-quietly-releases-gpt-3-5/">release of GPT-3.5</a>.<br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/shein-jumps-on-the-third-party-brandwagon-with-alibaba-veteran/"><strong>A new face</strong></a>: Shein is embracing its third-party business by bringing on Jessica Liu, the former co-president at the Southeast Asian e-commerce giant Lazada. <a href="https://twitter.com/ritacyliao" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rita</a> has more.<br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/india-wont-enforce-market-share-cap-on-upi-until-2025-in-a-win-for-google-and-walmart/"><strong>One surprising delay for India, one giant “whew” for retailers</strong></a>: <a href="https://twitter.com/refsrc" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Manish</a> writes that India is delaying a market share cap on the Unified Payments Interface payments network until 2025. This is a win — for now — for companies like Google and Walmart, which own a large share of it.</p>
<h2>Startups and VC</h2>
<p>Smoodi wants to see its smoothies in the hands of, well, everyone, and it <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/smoodi-robotic-smart-blender-series-a/">closed $5 million to expand the reach for its robotic smart blender</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/ChristineMHall" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Christine</a> reports. Not gonna lie: we prefer smoothie robots over robots being used to kill people. See <a href="https://twitter.com/bheater" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian</a>’s article about how <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/san-francisco-police-can-now-use-robots-to-kill/">the police department in San Francisco can now use robots to kill people</a>. In other robot news, also from Brian, <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/monarch-delivers-its-first-robot-tractor/">Monarch delivers its first “smart tractor.”</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, it seems like Mozilla is on a buying spree. Today, <a href="https://twitter.com/kyle_l_wiggers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kyle</a> reports that it <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/mozilla-acquires-active-replica-to-build-on-its-metaverse-vision/">acquired Active Replica to build on its metaverse vision</a>, and yesterday, <a href="https://twitter.com/psawers" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Paul</a> wrote that <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/mozilla-acquires-the-team-behind-pulse-an-automated-status-update-tool-for-slack/">the company snapped up the team behind Pulse</a>, an automated status updater for Slack.</p>
<p>Another fistful of news stories to brighten your day:</p>
<p><strong>Hitting the brakes</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/kirstenkorosec" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kirsten</a> reports that Hyundai-backed autonomous vehicle startup <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/hyundai-aptiv-backed-av-startup-motional-cuts-workforce/">Motional cuts workforce</a>.<br />
<strong>From container ships to $60,000 Jet Skis</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/haje" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Haje</a> reports that YC-backed Boundary Layer pivots <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/boundary-layer-personal-watercraft-pivot/">from container ships to hydrofoiling personal watercraft</a>, despite claiming to have $90 million worth of preorders for the former.<br />
<strong>We can still go deeper</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/cookie" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Connie</a> speaks with a secondary market pro who thinks <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/this-secondary-market-pro-thinks-we-havent-hit-bottom-but-he-sees-price-drops-slowing/">we haven’t hit bottom quite yet</a>, but he sees the price drops slowing, finally.<br />
<strong>Uncovering skincare</strong>: Kenya’s <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/kenyas-uncover-raises-1m-to-expand-skincare-product-enterprise-across-africa/">Uncover raises $1 million to expand skincare</a> product enterprise across Africa, <a href="https://twitter.com/annienjanja" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Annie</a> reports.<br />
<strong>You, but artier</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/asilbwrites" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amanda</a> reports that <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/lensa-ai-climbs-the-app-store-charts-as-its-magic-avatars-go-viral/">Lensa AI climbs the App Store charts </a>as its AI-enhanced “magic avatars” that look like you go hella viral.</p>
<h2>Pitch Deck Teardown: Hour One’s $20M Series A deck</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> TechCrunch</p>
</div>
<p>Startups are approaching language learning from every angle: Hour One uses AI to deploy avatars that turn text into video.</p>
<p>In 2020, its founders raised a $5 million seed round, but earlier this year, it raised $20 million more via a Series A. Here’s a complete breakdown of the company’s unredacted 11-slide deck:</p>
<p>Cover slide<br />
“At a glance” summary slide<br />
Solution slide<br />
Market size slide<br />
Value proposition slide<br />
Product slide 1<br />
Product slide 2<br />
Target audience slide<br />
Case study slide<br />
Team slide<br />
Closing slide</p>
<p>Haje takes a look at the good, the bad, and the ugly in the company’s $20 million series A pitch deck:</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/pitch-deck-teardown-hour-ones-20m-series-a-deck/">Pitch Deck Teardown: Hour One’s $20M Series A deck</a></p>

</div>
<p>Three more from the TC+ team:</p>
<p><strong>Bird is the word</strong>:<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/birds-plan-to-stay-in-the-shared-scooter-game/"> Bird’s plan to stay in the shared scooter game,</a> by<a href="https://twitter.com/RebeccaBellan" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Rebecca</a>.<br />
<strong>Robots writing words</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/alex" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alex</a> is relieved that <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/chatgpt-isnt-putting-me-out-of-a-job-yet-but-its-very-good-fun/">ChatGPT isn’t putting him out of a job yet,</a> concluding that it’s a lot of fun.<br />
<strong>Going down, in some places</strong>:<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/startup-valuations-are-declining-but-not-consistently/"> Startup valuations are declining — but not consistently</a>, writes <a href="https://twitter.com/rebecca_szkutak" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Becca</a> in her latest piece.</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/techcrunchplus/"><em>TechCrunch+</em></a><em> is our membership program that helps founders and startup teams get ahead of the pack.</em><a href="https://link.techcrunch.com/click/26685582.342535/aHR0cHM6Ly90ZWNoY3J1bmNoLmNvbS9zdWJzY3JpYmUvP3V0bV9tZWRpdW09VENuZXdzbGV0dGVyJnRwY2M9VENkYWlseW5ld3NsZXR0ZXI/6036d5494a049802a929497cBf82fd2bd"><em> You can sign up here</em></a><em>. Use code “DC” for a 15% discount on an annual subscription!</em></p>
<h2>Big Tech Inc.</h2>
<p>As we sift through <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1598752139278532610">Elon Musk’s tweet regarding hate speech today</a>, we have to point out there’s been a lot of “FAFO” going on in the Twitterverse, and Kanye West is the latest to FO what happens when he FAs. Just a little over a month after Kanye was reinstated on Twitter, <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/elon-musk-suspends-kanye-wests-account-for-breaking-twitter-rules/">Elon Musk suspended his account</a> again for breaking the social media giant’s rules,<a href="https://twitter.com/indianidle" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Ivan</a> writes. This also comes as West decides he <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/kanye-west-isnt-buying-parler-after-all/">isn’t buying Parler </a>after all. <a href="https://twitter.com/etherington" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Darrell</a> has more.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, in the world of corporate shake-ups, <a href="https://twitter.com/bayareawriter" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mary Ann</a> delivers a primo headline for her <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/when-one-door-closes-opendoor-ceo-eric-wu-steps-down-cfo-carrie-wheeler-steps-in-as-new-chief-executive/">story on Opendoor’s CEO Eric Wu</a>, who stepped down today, while <a href="https://twitter.com/breadfrom" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Aria</a> reports that space company Astra is restructuring its management team <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/">after Benjamin Lyon resigns</a>.</p>
<p>Enjoy the start of your weekend with four more:</p>
<p><strong>Breaker, we got ourselves a semi</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/RebeccaBellan" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rebecca</a> brings us news that Tesla delivered its <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/tesla-reveals-long-awaited-semi-truck-and-begins-first-deliveries/">long-awaited Semi truck</a> and that the car maker is<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/tesla-offers-3750-discount-for-model-3-model-y-deliveries-in-december/"> offering a discount</a> for its Model 3, Model Y deliveries in December.<br />
<strong>Exposed in the Sunshine State</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/zackwhittaker" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zack</a> writes that a security flaw in Florida’s state tax website<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/florida-tax-bug-data-exposed/"> led to the exposure of hundreds of filers’ data</a>.<br />
<strong>More representation</strong>: Activision Blizzard workers in Albany <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/activision-blizzard-workers-in-albany-vote-to-form-the-companys-second-union/">voted to form a union</a>, the company’s second one,<a href="https://twitter.com/asilbwrites" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Amanda</a> reports.<br />
<strong>Just in time?</strong>: Payment giant Stripe is the latest to offer a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/stripe-announces-fiat-to-crypto-onramp-widget/">fiat-to-crypto on-ramp widget</a> so that people can hold cryptocurrencies without having to sign up for a currency exchange. <a href="https://twitter.com/romaindillet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Romain</a> has more.</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/daily-crunch-chatgpts-user-experience-and-implementation-should-have-google-scared/">Daily Crunch: ChatGPT’s user experience and implementation ‘should have Google scared’</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/christine-hall/">Christine Hall</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/daily-crunch-chatgpts-user-experience-and-implementation-should-have-google-scared/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Looks like sex tech startup Lora DiCarlo is done for</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/looks-like-sex-tech-startup-lora-dicarlo-is-done-for/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/looks-like-sex-tech-startup-lora-dicarlo-is-done-for/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/looks-like-sex-tech-startup-lora-dicarlo-is-done-for/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lora DiCarlo, a sex tech startup that made headlines in 2019 after being blacklisted from the Consumer Electronics Show, seems to have shut down. The company’s website is offline and reportedly orders have gone unfulfilled for months. TechCrunch has reached out to the eponymous founder for confirmation, but it sure looks like the end of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lora DiCarlo, a sex tech startup that made headlines in 2019 after being blacklisted from the Consumer Electronics Show, seems to have shut down. The company’s website is offline and reportedly orders have gone unfulfilled for months.</p>
<p>TechCrunch has reached out to the eponymous founder for confirmation, but it sure looks like the end of the line for a briefly promising high-tech sex toy enterprise.</p>
<p>Founded in 2017, Lora DiCarlo was one of a new wave of tech-forward sexual health companies headed up by women. It won an innovation award at CES 2019 for, as our writer put it at the time, “a hands-free device that uses biomimicry and robotics to help women achieve a blended orgasm by simultaneously stimulating the G-spot and the clitoris.”</p>
<p>But then the Consumer Technology Association, which runs CES, <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/01/08/ces-revokes-award-from-female-founded-sex-tech-company/">withdrew the award and banned the company</a> from exhibiting at the show. Their explanation at the time was that neither the company nor its devices “fit a product category.”</p>
<p>Predictably, this attracted immediate blowback and allegations of sexism, prudery and generally bad judgment. Everyone was on Lora DiCarlo’s side, and the publicity was invaluable, <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/10/03/lora-dicarlo-founder-says-ces-award-snub-did-company-a-pretty-big-favor/">she later told TechCrunch at Disrupt</a>: “I think they actually did us a pretty big favor.” The company raised $2 million around that time, and about $9 million total over its five years of operation.</p>
<p>But despite a big return to the show in 2020 (and a coveted <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/01/10/a-sex-tech-startups-triumphant-return-to-ces/">TC+ feature</a>, of course), the company seems to have faltered during the pandemic — perhaps falling victim to the same chip shortages and manufacturing problems even established hardware makers encountered.</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/01/10/a-sex-tech-startups-triumphant-return-to-ces/">A sex tech startup’s triumphant return to CES</a></p>

</div>
<p>As <a href="https://www.womens-health.com/lora-dicarlo-offline" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chronicled by Women’s Health</a>, the last few months seem to have been Lora DiCarlo’s last, as various aspects of a functioning commercial enterprise began to fail: orders weren’t going out, stock was gone at retail partners and personnel have left. The site went down earlier this month and is down still. Although there has not been any official announcement, it certainly does seem that the company is kaput.</p>
<p>It’s too bad, but finding success as a hardware startup is hard enough without a pandemic and the stigma on sex toys adding drag. We’ll update this article if we hear back from DiCarlo.</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/looks-like-sextech-startup-lora-dicarlo-is-done-for/">Looks like sex tech startup Lora DiCarlo is done for</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/devin-coldewey/">Devin Coldewey</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/looks-like-sex-tech-startup-lora-dicarlo-is-done-for/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk vicariously publishes internal emails from Twitter’s Hunter Biden laptop drama</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-vicariously-publishes-internal-emails-from-twitters-hunter-biden-laptop-drama/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-vicariously-publishes-internal-emails-from-twitters-hunter-biden-laptop-drama/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-vicariously-publishes-internal-emails-from-twitters-hunter-biden-laptop-drama/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk reminded his followers on Friday that owning Twitter now means he controls every aspect of the company — including what its employees said behind closed doors before he took over. Earlier this week, Musk teased the release of what he called “The Twitter Files,” declaring that the public “deserves to know what really [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk reminded his followers on Friday that owning Twitter now means he controls every aspect of the company — including what its employees said behind closed doors before he took over.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, Musk teased the release of <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1597336812732575744">what he called “The Twitter Files,”</a> declaring that the public “deserves to know what really happened” behind the scenes during Twitter’s <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/10/16/twitter-new-york-post/">decision to stifle a story about Hunter Biden back in 2020</a>.</p>
<p>On Friday evening, Musk delivered, sort of. Twitter’s new owner shared a thread from author and Substack writer Matt Taibbi who is apparently now in possession of the trove of internal documents, which he opted to painstakingly share one tweet at a time, in narrative form.</p>
<p>Taibbi noted on his Substack that he had to “agree to certain conditions” in order to land the story, though he declined to elaborate about what the conditions were. (We’d suspect that sharing the documents in tweet form to boost the platform’s engagement must have been on the list.)</p>

<p>Taibbi’s decision to reveal a selection of the documents one tweet at a time was apparently not painstaking enough. One screenshot, now deleted, published Jack Dorsey’s private personal email address. Another shared an unredacted personal email belonging to Rep. Ro Khanna (D-CA), who expressed concerns about Twitter’s action at the time. Both incidents appear to run afoul of <a href="https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/personal-information">Twitter’s anti-doxing policy.</a></p>
<p>The documents, which are mostly internal Twitter emails, depict the chaotic situation that led Twitter to censor a New York Post story about Hunter Biden two years ago. In October 2020, The New York Post published a story that <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/10/16/twitter-new-york-post/">cited materials</a> purportedly obtained from a laptop that the younger Biden left at a repair shop. With a presidential election around the corner and 2016’s hacked DNC emails and other Russian election meddling fresh in mind, Twitter decided to <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/10/14/suspect-provenance-of-hunter-biden-data-cache-prompts-skepticism-and-social-media-bans/">limit the story’s reach</a>.</p>
<div class="piano-inline-promo"></div>
<p>In conversation with members of Twitter’s comms and policy teams, Twitter’s former Head of Trust and Safety Yoel Roth cited the company’s rules about hacked materials and noted the “severe risks and lessons of 2016” that influenced the decision making.</p>
<p>One member of Twitter’s legal team wrote that it was “reasonable” for Twitter to assume that the documents came from a hack, adding that “caution is warranted.” “We simply need more information,” he wrote.</p>
<p>In his Twitter thread, Taibbi <a href="https://twitter.com/mtaibbi/status/1598834231794315265">characterized</a> the situation to make such a consequential enforcement decision without consulting the company’s CEO as unusual. In reality, then-CEO Jack Dorsey was well known for being hands-off at the company, at times working remotely from a private island in the South Pacific and delegating <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/16/technology/twitter-donald-trump-jack-dorsey.html">even high profile decisions</a> to his policy team.</p>
<p>After Twitter acted, the response from outside the company was swift — and included one Democrat, apparently. “… In the heat of a Presidential campaign, restricting dissemination of newspaper articles (even if NY Post is far right) seems like it will invite more backlash than it will do good,” Khanna wrote to a member of Twitter’s policy team.</p>
<p>At the time, Facebook took similar measures. But Twitter was alone in its unprecedented decision to block links to the story, ultimately inciting a firestorm of criticism that the website was putting a thumb on the scale for Democrats. The company, its former CEO and some policy executives have since described the incident as a mistake made out of an over-abundance of caution — a story that checks out in light of the newly published emails.</p>
<p>Musk hyped the release of the emails as a smoking gun, but they mostly tell us what we already knew: that Twitter, fearful of a repeat of 2016, took an unusual moderation step when it probably should have provided context and let the story circulate. Musk has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1519073003933515776">apparently stewed over the issue</a> since at least April when he called the decision to suspend the Post’s account “incredibly inappropriate.”</p>
<p>Files from the laptop would later be <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2022/03/30/hunter-biden-laptop-data-examined/">verified by other news outlets</a>, but in the story’s early days no one was able to corroborate that the documents were real and not manipulated, including social platforms. “Most of the data obtained by The Post lacks cryptographic features that would help experts make a reliable determination of authenticity, especially in a case where the original computer and its hard drive are not available for forensic examination,” the Washington Post wrote in its own story verifying the emails. The decision inspired Twitter to change its rules around <a href="https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/hacked-materials">sharing hacked materials</a>.</p>
<p>Twitter’s former Head of Trust and Safety Yoel Roth shared more insight about the decision in an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4l1INc-rM5M">interview earlier this week</a>, noting that the story set off “alarm bells” signaling that it might be a hack and leak campaign by Russian group APT28, also known as Fancy Bear. “Ultimately for me, it didn’t reach a place where I was comfortable removing this content from Twitter,” Roth said.</p>
<p>Dorsey admitted fault at the time in a roundabout way. “Straight blocking of URLs was wrong, and we updated our policy and enforcement to fix,” Dorsey tweeted. “Our goal is to attempt to add context,” he said, adding that now the company could do that by labeling hacked materials.</p>
<p>Musk has been preoccupied with a handful of specific content moderation decisions since <a href="https://twitter.com/SethDillon/status/1511325246967660547">before deciding to buy the company</a>. His frustration that Twitter suspended the conservative satire site The Babylon Bee over a transphobic tweet appears to be the reason he even <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-04-05/elon-musk-opined-about-buying-twitter-after-babylon-bee-ban">decided to buy Twitter</a> to begin with.</p>
<p>Now two years after it happened, the Hunter Biden social media controversy is still a sore spot for conservatives, right wing media and Twitter’s new ownership. The platform’s past policy controversies are mostly irrelevant now with Musk at the wheel, but he apparently still has an axe to grind with the Twitter of yore — and we’re seeing that unfold in real(ish) time.</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2020/10/16/twitter-new-york-post/">Twitter is now allowing users to share that controversial New York Post story</a></p>

</div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/elon-musk-vicariously-publishes-internal-emails-from-twitters-hunter-biden-laptop-drama/">Elon Musk vicariously publishes internal emails from Twitter’s Hunter Biden laptop drama</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/taylor-hatmaker/">Taylor Hatmaker</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/elon-musk-vicariously-publishes-internal-emails-from-twitters-hunter-biden-laptop-drama/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tech’s growth story shifted this year. How has that impacted transparency?</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/techs-growth-story-shifted-this-year-how-has-that-impacted-transparency/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/techs-growth-story-shifted-this-year-how-has-that-impacted-transparency/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/techs-growth-story-shifted-this-year-how-has-that-impacted-transparency/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When Vijay Chattha was building a startup, his competitor was what some would call a media darling. The competition had a good story, which created investor interest. In turn, that interest helped land key customers. And so the cycle repeated. Chattha eventually sold that company in a lukewarm exit and took with him an important [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Vijay Chattha was building a startup, his competitor was what some would call a media darling. The competition had a good story, which created investor interest. In turn, that interest helped land key customers. And so the cycle repeated. <a href="https://twitter.com/vijaychattha" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chattha</a> eventually sold that company in a lukewarm exit and took with him an important lesson: Earned media has the power to be a kingmaker.</p>
<p>Chattha is now the founder and CEO of VSC, a public relations firm that has helped launch over 600 companies. The firm works with startups across all stages and recently introduced a $21 million venture firm to back the companies that it advises. (Or, as Chattha puts it, to put some skin in the game).</p>
<p>Now, 20 years in, Chattha has thoughts regarding how tech’s cyclical nature has impacted its relationship with media, the power of sharing real numbers and whether founders should prepare to fall on their sword in the name of transparency.</p>

<div class="article-block block--pullout block--right">
<p>			“I think it’s a dangerous thing. It’s like water. If you don’t have publicity, you can be dehydrated. But if you have too much you can drown.”							Vijay Chattha</p></div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/startup-pitching-storytelling-tech-pr-2022/">My entire conversation with the entrepreneur</a> can be found wherever you listen to podcasts, so <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/startup-pitching-storytelling-tech-pr-2022/">take a listen</a> if you prefer audio over words (in that case, what are you doing here‽).</p>
<p>Below, we extracted several key excerpts from the interview for your reading pleasure.</p>
<p><strong>What’s your temperature reading on how vulnerable founders are right now when it comes to sharing hardships publicly? </strong></p>
<p>Vijay Chattha: It depends on the founder. Is it their first startup, their second or their third? Generally what I find is the more successful and the more wisdom you have, the more transparent you are over time, and possibly even cynical, right? But the first-time founders, they’re under a lot of pressure [to do] whatever the VCs or hired people around them are telling them to do. They’ve got to do it. They’re very concerned that the competitors are reading this stuff.</p>

<div class="extra-crunch-offer-container"></div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/03/techs-growth-story-shifted-this-year-how-has-that-impacted-transparency/">Tech’s growth story shifted this year. How has that impacted transparency?</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/natasha-mascarenhas/">Natasha Mascarenhas</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/03/techs-growth-story-shifted-this-year-how-has-that-impacted-transparency/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Astra star hire Benjamin Lyon resigns, management team restructured</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Space company Astra’s management team is undergoing another shake-up. The company said Friday that chief engineer Benjamin Lyon has resigned after just short of two years in the role. Rather than seek a replacement for that position, Astra promoted four key staff to management positions that will now directly report to CEO Chris Kemp and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Space company Astra’s management team is undergoing another shake-up. The company said Friday that chief engineer Benjamin Lyon has resigned after just short of two years in the role. Rather than seek a replacement for that position, Astra promoted four key staff to management positions that will now directly report to CEO Chris Kemp and other C-Suite staff.</p>
<p>Astra <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/02/17/astra-hires-longtime-apple-veteran-benjamin-lyon-as-chief-engineer/">hired Lyon in February 2021</a>, after a two-decade-plus career at Apple. The move from consumer electronics to rockets may have been unconventional, but at the time CEO Chris Kemp was adamant that the company sought someone from outside the aerospace industry.</p>
<p>In an interview with TechCrunch on today’s news, Kemp said it was a “very well-coordinated and collaborative transition.”</p>
<p>“[Lyon] hired a bunch of star players,” he said. “One thing that became pretty clear to all of us was the caliber of his team and the opportunity to elevate them onto our management team would really streamline things.”</p>
<p>Kemp added that Lyon had an opportunity to join a Fortune 500 company in a C-level position, and that at least two of the promotions — Giovanni Greco, who is now leading launch system delivery, and Jonathan Donaldson, who will lead Astra Spacecraft Engine delivery — were green-lighted around a month ago. The other promotions include Doug Kunzman to lead launch and test operations and Bryson Gentile to lead manufacturing.</p>
<p>These are far from the only recent changes to Astra’s workforce. In September, the company announced that it was bringing on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/09/30/astras-bringing-on-axel-martinez-as-new-cfo/">a new CFO, Axel Martinez</a>, as the company seeks to grow its spacecraft business and accelerate development of its launch system and Rocket 4.0. Two months later, the company saw the departure of VP of communications Kati Dahm.</p>
<p>Amid these staff changes, Astra also laid off 16% of its workforce. In a fourth-quarter earnings call with investors, executives said they anticipate payroll savings from the layoffs to be realized in the first quarter of next year.</p>
<div class="piano-inline-promo"></div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/">Astra star hire Benjamin Lyon resigns, management team restructured</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/aria-alamalhodaei/">Aria Alamalhodaei</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/astra-star-hire-benjamin-lyon-resigns-management-team-restructured/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TechCrunch+ roundup: Cash management basics, proptech investor survey, visa interview prep</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-roundup-cash-management-basics-proptech-investor-survey-visa-interview-prep/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-roundup-cash-management-basics-proptech-investor-survey-visa-interview-prep/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-roundup-cash-management-basics-proptech-investor-survey-visa-interview-prep/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A few years ago, I was driving in a rural area on the coast north of San Francisco and found myself low on gas. In fact, the fuel light was flashing urgently. My cell phone couldn’t get a signal to direct me to the nearest gas station, so I put the engine in economy mode [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A few years ago, I was driving in a rural area on the coast north of San Francisco and found myself low on gas. In fact, the fuel light was flashing urgently.</p>
<p>My cell phone couldn’t get a signal to direct me to the nearest gas station, so I put the engine in economy mode and drove on instinct. I knew the car had a reserve tank, but I had no idea how far it would take me.</p>
<p>Founders who don’t implement proper treasury management practices during a downturn are as foolhardy as I was that day — how far can your company go on fumes?</p>
<p>“Your cash reserves mean nothing if you aren’t able to access them in time to pay for your ongoing expenses,” writes Michael Dombrowski, corporate treasury adviser at Rho.</p>
<p>In a TC+ guest post, he shares the <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/treasury-management-should-be-top-of-mind-for-startup-founders/">basic steps for creating a cash management plan</a> for startups that have closed an extension or need to make the most out of their precious runway.</p>
<p>Full TechCrunch+ articles are only available to members<br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/subscribe/">Use discount code <strong>TCPLUSROUNDUP</strong></a> to save 20% off a one- or two-year subscription</p>
<p>TechCrunch+ is hiring for several roles, including a part-time desk editor who will help manage our guest contributor program.</p>
<p>If you’re interested, please don’t contact me — you can find more information about this role and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/jobs/view/3377610494/?refId=xLfReeh%2FQKST2B0lNSXckw%3D%3D" target="_blank" rel="noopener">submit an application via LinkedIn</a>.</p>
<p>Thanks very much for reading, and have a great weekend.</p>
<p>Walter Thompson<br />
Editorial Manager, TechCrunch+<br />
<a href="https://www.twitter.com/yourprotagonist" target="_blank" rel="noopener">@yourprotagonist</a></p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/treasury-management-should-be-top-of-mind-for-startup-founders/">Treasury management should be top of mind for startup founders</a></p>

</div>
<h2>Move over, operators — consultants are the new nontraditional VC</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> Getty Images</p>
</div>
<p>In the first half of this year, 30 funds received almost two-thirds of all new venture capital raised, according to PitchBook.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Rebecca Szkutak found that several consulting firms that help early-stage startups get to the next level are now launching their own VC funds.</p>
<p>“Over the last two to three years we’ve been asked by a lot of founders to join their cap table,” said FNDR founder and CEO James Vincent.</p>
<p>“The founder wants us on the journey. We’ve spent time with them and shown great intimacy. We don’t do it with everybody.”</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/28/move-over-operators-consultants-are-the-new-nontraditional-vc/">Move over, operators — consultants are the new nontraditional VC</a></p>

</div>
<h2>Strategic warfare: How to hire and retain top analytics talent</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> <a href="https://www.gettyimages.in/search/photographer?photographer=designer491" target="_blank" rel="noopener">designer491 <span class="screen-reader-text">(opens in a new window)</span></a> / Getty Images</p>
</div>
<p>Especially in the early days, non-technical founders are vulnerable when it comes to hiring technical employees. How can you tell if someone can deliver when you don’t have experience doing the job yourself?</p>
<p>Analytics can be as much of a black box as engineering, which is why hiring managers need to look past the skill list on CVs to find more effective ways to sort candidates, writes Chuck Soha, managing director at StoneTurn.</p>
<p>In an article that includes suggested pre-screening techniques and sample questions, he says companies should rely on case studies during the interview process, “which ultimately makes the experience better both for the employee and the employer.”</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/strategic-warfare-how-to-hire-and-retain-top-analytics-talent/">Strategic warfare: How to hire and retain top analytics talent</a></p>

</div>
<h2>Proptech in Review: 3 investors explain why they’re bullish on tech that makes buildings greener</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> <a href="https://www.gettyimages.in/search/photographer?photographer=AndriyOnufriyenko" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Andriy Onufriyenko <span class="screen-reader-text">(opens in a new window)</span></a> / Getty Images</p>
</div>
<div class="piano-inline-promo"></div>
<p>Investors who work at the intersection of climate tech and proptech seek out potentially profitable startups that can reduce emissions and enhance the built environment.</p>
<p>It’s a high-stakes balancing act with significant risk, but considering the upside for category winners and the health of the planet, “the potential market is enormous,” reports Tim De Chant.</p>
<p>For his second proptech investor survey in a three-part series, he interviewed:</p>
<p>Jake Fingert, managing partner, and Lionel Foster, investor, Camber Creek<br />
Anja Rath, managing partner, PropTech1 Ventures<br />
Othmane Zrikem, chief data officer, A/O Proptech</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/proptech-in-review-3-investors-explain-why-theyre-bullish-on-tech-that-makes-buildings-greener/">Proptech in Review: 3 investors explain why they’re bullish on tech that makes buildings greener</a></p>

</div>
<h2>Dear Sophie: How should I prepare for my visa interview?</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> Bryce Durbin/TechCrunch</p>
</div>
<p><strong>Dear Sophie,</strong></p>
<p><strong>Our startup was just accepted into the winter batch of a top accelerator!</strong></p>
<p><strong>My co-founder with an H-1B just got laid off from Big Tech, but he’s OK because his immigration lawyer is filing a change of status to B-1 within the 60-day grace period. I’m nervous though, because I’m outside the U.S. and I don’t yet have a B-1/B-2 visitor visa.</strong></p>
<p><strong>How can I ace the visa interview? What type of questions will I be asked? How should I prepare?</strong></p>
<p><strong>— Tenacious in Tobago</strong></p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/dear-sophie-how-should-i-prepare-for-my-visa-interview/">Dear Sophie: How should I prepare for my visa interview?</a></p>

</div>
<h2>5 methods for leveraging digital advertising during a downturn</h2>

<div class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> <a href="https://www.gettyimages.in/search/photographer?photographer=RichardDrury" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Richard Drury <span class="screen-reader-text">(opens in a new window)</span></a> / Getty Images</p>
</div>
<p>When Apple offered its customers greater privacy control, it upended mobile advertising. According to a survey by data science company Proxima, 40% of respondents said the iOS privacy policy change negatively impacted their business.</p>
<p>To stay flexible, Proxima CEO Alex Song says marketers should experiment with shifting their campaigns to platforms like TikTok, Snapchat and Instagram.</p>
<p>“For the remainder of 2022 and beyond, the decision is not whether to advertise, but where, how much and how to augment performance.”</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/5-ways-consumer-startups-can-leverage-digital-advertising-in-a-downturn/">5 methods for leveraging digital advertising during a downturn</a></p>

</div>
<h2>Pitch Deck Teardown: Hour One’s $20M Series A deck</h2>

<div class="wp-caption alignnone">
<p class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Image Credits:</strong> TechCrunch</p>
</div>
<p>Startups are approaching language learning from every angle: Hour One uses AI to deploy avatars that turn text into video.</p>
<p>In 2020, its founders raised a $5 million seed round, but earlier this year, it raised $20 million more via a Series A. Here’s a complete breakdown of the company’s unredacted 11-slide deck:</p>
<p>Cover slide<br />
“At a glance” summary slide<br />
Solution slide<br />
Market size slide<br />
Value proposition slide<br />
Product slide 1<br />
Product slide 2<br />
Target audience slide<br />
Case study slide<br />
Team slide<br />
Closing slide</p>
<div class="embed breakout">
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/01/pitch-deck-teardown-hour-ones-20m-series-a-deck/">Pitch Deck Teardown: Hour One’s $20M Series A deck</a></p>

</div>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-roundup-cash-management-basics-proptech-investor-survey-visa-interview-prep/">TechCrunch+ roundup: Cash management basics, proptech investor survey, visa interview prep</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/walter-thompson/">Walter Thompson</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-roundup-cash-management-basics-proptech-investor-survey-visa-interview-prep/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salesforce CEO succession drama and other TC news</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/salesforce-ceo-succession-drama-and-other-tc-news/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/salesforce-ceo-succession-drama-and-other-tc-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/salesforce-ceo-succession-drama-and-other-tc-news/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This week, I talk with Rita Liao about the great wall of porn obscuring information about protests in china. And Ron Miller comes on to recap the AWS re:invent event and his story on Salesforce co-CEO Bret Taylor stepping down. And as always, we break down the biggest stories in tech. Articles from the episode: [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, I talk with <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/rita-liao/">Rita Liao</a> about the great wall of porn obscuring information about protests in china. And <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/ronjourn/">Ron Miller</a> comes on to recap the AWS re:invent event and his story on Salesforce co-CEO Bret Taylor stepping down. And as always, we break down the biggest stories in tech.</p>
<p>Articles from the episode:</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/28/great-wall-of-porn-obscures-china-protest-news-on-twitter/">Great Wall of porn obscures China protest news on Twitter </a><br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/bret-taylor-steps-down-as-co-chair-and-ceo-of-salesforce/">Bret Taylor steps down as co-chair and CEO of Salesforce</a><br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/tag/aws/">All of TC’s AWS re:invent converage</a></p>
<p>Other news from the week:</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/28/instafest-app-lets-you-create-your-own-festival-lineup-from-spotify/">Instafest app lets you create your own festival lineup from Spotify</a><br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/30/elon-musk-twitter-eu-dsa-warning/">Musk at Twitter has ‘huge work’ ahead to comply with EU rules, warns bloc</a><br />
<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/11/29/apple-announces-winners-of-the-app-store-awards-for-2022/">BeReal wins ‘app of the year’ in Apple’s annual App Store Awards in 2022</a></p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/salesforce-ceo-succession-drama-and-other-tc-news/">Salesforce CEO succession drama and other TC news</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/darrell-etherington/">Darrell Etherington</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/salesforce-ceo-succession-drama-and-other-tc-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TechCrunch wants to meet your startup at CES 2023</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We’re a month out from the next CES. TechCrunch is returning to Vegas for the first time a few years and — as usual — we’re on the hunt for the most fascinating startups. Work for a startup showing off a cool new product at CES next month? Let us know by filling out the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’re a month out from the next CES. TechCrunch is returning to Vegas for the first time a few years and — as usual — we’re on the hunt for the most fascinating startups.</p>
<p>Work for a startup showing off a cool new product at CES next month? Let us know by filling out the below form. Our team will be reaching out to those companies we think we will be a good fit for coverage.</p>
<p>Thanks, good luck and see you in Las Vegas!</p>
<p>Loading…</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/tag/ces-2023"></a></p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/">TechCrunch wants to meet your startup at CES 2023</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/brian-heater/">Brian Heater</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/techcrunch-wants-to-meet-your-startup-at-ces-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The final 12-hours to savings on passes to TC Sessions: Space</title>
		<link>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/the-final-12-hours-to-savings-on-passes-to-tc-sessions-space/</link>
					<comments>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/the-final-12-hours-to-savings-on-passes-to-tc-sessions-space/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/the-final-12-hours-to-savings-on-passes-to-tc-sessions-space/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Calling out to the die-hard procrastinators, last-minute decision makers and all you head-down-get-it-done types. TC Sessions: Space 2022 takes place next week on December 6, but you have just 12 short hours left before the price of admission heads into a higher stratosphere. It’s now o’clock: Hop off the fence already and save. Buy a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Calling out to the die-hard procrastinators, last-minute decision makers and all you head-down-get-it-done types. <a href="https://techcrunch.com/events/tc-sessions-space-2022/?promo=post_12hours_dec2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TC Sessions: Space 2022</a> takes place next week on December 6, but you have just 12 short hours left before the price of admission heads into a higher stratosphere.</p>
<p><strong>It’s now o’clock:</strong> Hop off the fence already and save. <a href="https://techcrunch.com/events/tc-sessions-space-2022/?promo=post_12hours_dec2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Buy a pass</a> before <strong>December 2 at 11:59 p.m. PST</strong> — while they still cost $199. The price increases to $495 at midnight. Why pay more if you don’t have to?</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/events/tc-sessions-space-2022/#eef8e494-e8b7-4ee9-b1d0-64627c9dfc9f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The event agenda</a> is packed with experts and essential topics across the public, private and defense domains — including our partner sessions. Check them out below.</p>
<p><span class="gradient-text gradient-text--green-gradient"><strong>Bringing It to the Space Warfighting Domain</strong> </span></p>
<p>Space is playing an ever-greater role in modern warfare and in our broader national security. But delivering those critical space-based capabilities to warfighters and other end users is just one step in the increasingly complex mission life cycle.</p>
<p>From how to incorporate the latest innovations to what role commercial capabilities can play, the way our nation’s space programs acquire, deploy and operate next-generation systems is undergoing profound shifts. <strong>Charlie McGillis</strong> (Slingshot Aerospace), <strong>Jean L. Michael</strong> (Aerospace Corporation), <strong>Pete Muend</strong> (National Reconnaissance Office), <strong>Col. Joseph Roth</strong> (USSF Space Systems Command) and <strong>Christopher A. Solee</strong> (United States Space Command) will discuss how these pieces fit together to deliver needed capabilities and the opportunities to drive greater integration for the benefit of all. Sponsored by the Aerospace Corporation.</p>
<p><span class="gradient-text gradient-text--green-gradient"><strong>ISAM: A Commercial Linchpin for the New Space Economy</strong></span></p>
<div class="piano-inline-promo"></div>
<p>Large-scale commercial investments will dominate the next wave of space innovation, including commercial space stations in low Earth orbit (LEO) and technologies that will enable a permanent human presence on the moon. The United States has issued a national policy for developing In-Space Servicing, Assembly and Manufacturing (ISAM) capabilities that can operationally sustain the new space economy with efficiency and scale. This session encourages participants to roll up their sleeves, break past the 411 on ISAM and get practical about how to stimulate ISAM capability development. With <strong>Robert Hauge</strong> (SpaceLogistics) and <strong>Carolyn Mercer</strong> (National Aeronautics and Space Administration). Sponsored by the Aerospace Corporation.</p>
<p><span class="gradient-text gradient-text--green-gradient"><strong>Space Workforce 2030: Inspiring, Preparing and Employing the Next Generation</strong></span></p>
<p>The dawning space age offers enormous opportunities to explore new frontiers, grow the economy on orbit and strengthen our security. Making the most of this momentous time calls for an innovative workforce that can leverage diverse experiences and perspectives to solve the hard problems we’ll encounter.</p>
<p>The Space Workforce 2030 pledge is a first-of-its-kind effort launched earlier this year that is bringing together more than 30 of the country’s leading space companies to work collaboratively to increase diversity across our industry to build a vibrant workforce for the future. Hear from <strong>Michael Edmonds</strong> (Blue Origin), <strong>Steve Isakowitz</strong> (Aerospace Corporation) and <strong>Melanie Stricklan</strong> (Slingshot Aerospace) about the work they’re doing to inspire, prepare and employ the next generation of scientists and engineers and how you can play a part in supporting this vital mission. Sponsored by the Aerospace Corporation.</p>
<p><span class="gradient-text gradient-text--green-gradient"><strong>Hardware? What’s That? Why Software Is the Future of the Space Economy</strong></span></p>
<p>Launch gets all the press, but satellites and the software behind them are the workhorses of space. Hear from Antaris founder/CEO <strong>Tom Barton</strong> and Epsilon3 founder/CEO <strong>Laura Crabtree</strong> about how SaaS, open source and cloud-based platforms are revolutionizing the satellite industry and accelerating the space economy. They’ll also share what it’s like to be first-time founders, what it really takes to put good code into space and tips for fellow spacepreneurs. Sponsored by Antaris.</p>
<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/events/tc-sessions-space-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TC Sessions: Space 2022</a> takes place on December 6 in Los Angeles, but you have only 12 hours left until that $199 deal leaves orbit. <a href="https://techcrunch.com/events/tc-sessions-space-2022/#tickets" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Buy your pass</a> by <strong>December 2 at 11:59 p.m. PST</strong>. The price increases to $495 at midnight. Stop procrastinating and start saving!</p>
<p><em>Is your company interested in sponsoring or exhibiting at TC Sessions: Space? Contact our sponsorship sales team by </em><a href="http://info.techcrunch.com/SponsorshipsInterest.html?_ga=2.147735806.874617471.1572269011-985484541.1566312242" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>filling out this form</em></a><em>.</em></p>

<p><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/12/02/the-final-12-hours-to-savings-on-passes-to-tc-sessions-space/">The final 12-hours to savings on passes to TC Sessions: Space</a> by <a href="https://techcrunch.com/author/lauren-simonds-2/">Lauren Simonds</a> originally published on <a href="https://techcrunch.com/">TechCrunch</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://web.adil.asadqi.com/2022/12/02/the-final-12-hours-to-savings-on-passes-to-tc-sessions-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
